<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<project_data>
  <team_members>
    <member>
      <name>Faith Mulama</name>
      <role>Team Lead</role>
      <email>faithmulama@gmail.com</email>
    </member>
    <member>
      <name>Farida Selima</name>
      <role>Developer</role>
      <email>faridaashraf2006@gmail.com</email>
    </member>
  </team_members>
  <project_details>
    <title>Computer Science Ecosystems Group Project</title>
    <description>This project aims to equip foundation students with practical skills in Front-End Web Development, document typesetting, and data management.</description>
    <start_date>2024-07-03</start_date>
    <end_date>2024-07-11</end_date>
  </project_details>
  <technologies_used>
    <technology>
      <name>HTML</name>
      <version>5</version>
    </technology>
    <technology>
      <name>CSS</name>
      <version>3</version>
    </technology>
    <technology>
      <name>JavaScript</name>
      <version>ES6</version>
    </technology>
    <technology>
      <name>LaTeX</name>
      <version>2e</version>
    </technology>
    <technology>
      <name>XML</name>
      <version>1.0</version>
    </technology>
  </technologies_used>
  <deliverables>
    <deliverable>
      <name>HTML Webpage</name>
      <description>A basic HTML webpage featuring a form with CSS styling.HTML webpage features a form that allows users to input data, which is then processed and displayed using JavaScript. We used CSS to style the webpage, making it visually appealing and easy to use.</description>
    </deliverable>
    <deliverable>
      <name>CSS Stylesheet</name>
      <description>A CSS stylesheet that provides responsive design for the HTML webpage</description>
    </deliverable>
    <deliverable>
      <name>JavaScript Functionality</name>
      <description>JavaScript code that handles data submissions using the Fetch API.developed functionality using the JavaScript Fetch API to handle data submissions, emphasizing collaborative coding and problem-solving. This allowed us to create a dynamic and interactive webpage that responds to user input.</description>
    </deliverable>
    <deliverable>
      <name>LaTeX Document</name>
      <description>A LaTeX document that details the project's scope and findings.document was created as a team, detailing the project's scope and findings. We prepared the document with input from all team members, ensuring each section reflects the collaborative effort and understanding of the content.</description>
    </deliverable>
    <deliverable>
      <name>XML Document</name>
      <description>An XML document that represents structured data in a detailed and organized manner</description>
    </deliverable>
  </deliverables>
</project_data>